No, I'll fall... I'll never make it.
I'll never make it!
Ah, yes, I lose!
I'm failing!
What's wrong, what's wrong, what's wrong?
It's okay.
So, this is just a practice, so we'll start with a penalty game from now on.
This is the real thing.
There's always practice for this kind of thing, right?
It's no fun.
She's scary.
From here on out...
I don't care if it's fun or not.
What was the name of the project? What was the name of the project again?
Let's get serious.
Let's play with Moaka and entertain Moaka.
No, no, no, no, no. Let's be serious. Let's fight the block.
What? Did it change? What?
I didn't even know it was there.
It's a fight... a fight.
What? I didn't know it was like that.
I'm serious.
What?
Subscribe to our channel!
No games to play or anything?
It's a streaming service.
I have to do a lot of thinking to make sure everyone can watch.
I can't just go on and on and on with no notes.
I'm blocked at work.
I'm not allowed to play with my hands when I'm listening to someone.
I can do something.
I can do something like that.
But I have a good feeling about this game.
able to make...
Well, Hirata-sama's not here, so if Hitomachi loses, Hirata buys Hitomachi's bottom.
If one of us loses, Ohana will buy one of us a drink.
So, let's do it together in peace!
Yay!
Surprisingly, those who are resting don't care what anyone says.
Which one do you want to do first?
I don't know.
I don't mind going again.
Ah!
Hal!
Hal, you're bad.
Let's do it again.
Aah!
Ira!
Who are you?
What? There's nothing to play for.
We're in hell if we have anything to do with those two.
You're right.
I'm scared to do anything with those two.
I'm scared of them.
What? What's that?
Isn't that the worst? Scary.
I'm so scared.
Oh, my God, wait. Oh, my God.
That's the worst. No, I'm not gonna let you beat me again.
You want to do that?
No. Is that a possibility? No.
No. The one who loses this way...
I'm going to tell Hana that it's love.
The Amechele Project from Hell...
Mandatory entry.
Thank you, sir.
It's mandatory.
I can handle one hand now.
I'm going to win.
"I'm sure I'll win." That's funny.
I'll definitely win.
I've never seen such a strong fighting pose.
You have such a strong grip.
Let's do our best.
I don't want to lose this one.
I don't think we can lose.
Let's put it in the middle. Just right there. It's okay.
Wait a minute, wait a minute. It's a little crooked.
Maybe we don't need to worry about that. No, it's a little crooked.
It's a little crooked, but with that crookedness, it won't make any difference.
Oh, just a little more forward. I'll do it.
Okay, okay.
Okay, I'll go first.
First, get the stick!
What? Stick out?
I got a stick that says I'm a loser.
No, but we decided on the rules a while ago, or should I say, last time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It doesn't matter. It's the order of the game.
No, no, no, no.
It's a game, so...
No!
I'm going to put it back in until it's all filled in.
Start over.
What? It's not that easy.
No, let's just, uh, let's just put it down one time, and if we can't do it, then...
No, I can't.
Yes, I can't.
Try two.
Two what?
One more.
Okay, then?
I'll never be able to afford this one.
Can I get another one?
What do you say? Do you want another board?
Okay, okay.
It's an L-shaped board.
So we should put this on the board.
That's what I'm saying.
Okay, well, let's do it right.
I'm smart, so let's do it like this. - Okay.
Okay.
Like a jumbo pin.
That's cute.
Here we go.
There you go.
You can put six of your favorite things. What should we do with them?
What should I do with these?
You first.
You want to come out?
I really want to do it.
I think it's easier to put them here.
That's true.
I feel that way.
I'm...
Number one.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
You lose!
Yuko lost, too.
Last game, Ichikawa-san!
The rule was that you had to be born at least once.
No, you said three seconds ago...
You said that three seconds ago.
I don't have the stomach for this.
I don't.
Yes, sir.
He can't talk anymore.
Then show me your cute yuzu.
If you show me your cute yuzu for the camera, I'll make a decision based on that.
I'm kind of seeing it there.
So you'll take the moe dialogue or the hellish Irahana?
Ah, yes.
That's the ultimate choice.
Which one do you want?
I'm going to go with the moe line.
Oh, so it's something I'd be okay with.
Please show me.
Certainly.
I'm looking at it, so I'll start here.
Well, but I don't like the flowers.
I'm conflicted.
Wow! I beat Kyun-Miki.
Let me try again.
No, you can't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, not at all.
It's Kyun-Miki.
It's not enough.
Hey...
Stop it.
It's okay.
Stop it. Stop it.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh, what's with you all of a sudden? Thank you?
No, not at all. It was really cute.
Oh, she was cute?
Yeah, yeah.
I just thought so.
Oh, really? That's great. Thank you. Thank you.
I don't know.
You don't know? I don't know.
Wait, I'm afraid of what I might get.
Oh, come on...
This is how it ends.